Krzysztof Hoszowski

Software Engineer

Krzysztof Hoszowski

Wrocław, Poland

k-hoszowski@tutamail.com

linkedin.com/in/k-hoszowski github.com/k-hoszowski

About Me

Skills

I'm an interdisciplinary professional with a keen interest in free and open source software (FOSS), and years of diverse IT experiences. I'm open minded and willing to work with people of various backgrounds. I'm passionate and conscientious about what I do.

Adaptability and Flexibility

Collaboration and Teamwork

Rapid Learning of New Technologies

Strong Interpersonal Skills

Attention to Detail

Adjusting to Changing Requirements

Proficiency in Collaborative Tools

Continuous Skill Improvement

Openness to Feedback

Participation in Code Reviews and Pair Programming

Dedication to High-Quality Solutions

Windows: Registry, PowerShell

Linux: Bash, Threads, Processes, POSIX

Database Engineering: MySQL, LibreOffice Base Python: TensorFlow, NumPy, SciPy, Matplotlib

C++: Structured and Object-Oriented Programming

Java: Maven, Junit, Apache NetBeans

Web Development: PHP, JavaScript, Mermaid.js

Software Development: Strong understanding of software lifecycle and

development methodologies (Agile, Scrum, Waterfall) Version Control Systems: Git, GitHub, Oh My Git!

version control systems. Oit, Oit lab, Oil 141y Gr

Reports and Bachelor Thesis in LaTeX

Good at Explaining

Good at Reporting

Fast and Accurate Typing

Polish (Native)

English (Bilingual)

German (A1)

Experience

Lasertex sp. z o.o. / Software Engineer

Aug 2023 - Sep 2023, Wrocław, Poland

Delphi legacy code development. Developed interfaces for Windows users with metrological equipment, including:

- Lathe Measurement System LMS-5
- High Precision Laser Interferometer HPI-3D

Lasertex sp. z o.o. / Electronic Engineer

Jul 2023, Wrocław, Poland

Various entry-level positions, including:

- PCB Design: Utilized Altium Designer for creating and developing printed circuit board (PCB) layouts.
- LabVIEW Development: Interfaced and integrated LMS-5 sensors using LabVIEW for data acquisition and analysis.
- PCB and Cable Assembly: Performed manual assembly of PCBs and cables, ensuring precision and quality.
- Embedded Systems Programming: Developed and implemented embedded software solutions in C for hardware applications.

Politechnika Wrocławska / Computer Engineering Student

Oct 2020 - Jan 2024, Wrocław, Poland

- Bachelor thesis: Developed convolutional neural network (CNN) that predicts tonality of a song (music file). Completed despite very little and late assistance from supervisor.
- Coordinated and did software development for three university projects: optical lock, remotely controlled mapping robot (implemented in Arduino), gesture-controlled Snake game using supervised learning (implemented in Python). Graded A, B+, A.
- Individual pass of *Introduction to Programming* university course in C++: command-line application for constructing a hand-made tree data structure for brainstorming and mind-mapping.

Education

Politechnika Wrocławska / Bachelor's in Computer Engineering Oct 2020 - Jan 2024, Wrocław, Poland

Relevant coursework:

- Artificial Intelligence and Computer Vision
- Automation Using Bash Scripting (Linux)
- Physics Simulations in Mathematica and Matlab

Certifications

CCNA: Introduction to Networks Issued by Cisco Badge (click here to view)

References

Jyotiraditya V. Saraswat, **IBM** +48 516 872 512